BETHWEL RONO

Phone No: +254705302628

Gmail: betwelmusin@gmail.com/

bethwelmusin2017@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

My primary goal is to apply my technical expertise all throughout the full

software life cycle to ensure production and delivery of products and services that

meet client specifications. Along with a competent software developing team, and

with strong personal knowledge, skills, and experience in software engineering, I

am positive that this goal can be achieved. My experience as a junior software

developer enhanced my abilities in designing, implementing, testing, and

upgrading software. One of my objectives is to keep updated with the latest IT

trends and technologies. I am confident that if given the opportunity, I can be a

useful talent to the company.

EDUCATION

2017-2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE,

RONGO UNIVERSITY

2013-2016

KENYA CERTIFICATE OF SECONDARY EDUCATION,

TENGES BOYS HIGH SCHOOL

2004-2012

KENYA CERTIFICATE OF PRIMARY EDUCATION,

KABASIS PRIMARY SCHOOL

SKILLS

Web development and web services

• • C#, Python (Django), Angular, React js, RESTFUL API, web API, .NET Framework, and WordPress.

Database Management Systems

SQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Mongo DB

Design

- HTML & CSS,
- Bootstrap CSS, materialize CSS

Version Control.

GitHub. https://github.com/bethwelmusin

WORK EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2021- MARCH 2022: PONG AGENCIES LIMITED

Position: Software developer intern

Responsibilities

- 1. implement efficient and working software solutions
- 2. Design the project data flow
- 3. development of project backend
- 4. creating good user interface
- 5. work with the team in brainstorming the project requirements
- 6. Domain creation and hosting

JULY 2021-OCTOBER 2021: MICROPOINT SYSTEMS

Position: Junior Software Developer

Responsibilities

- 1. working with developers to design software, algorithms, flowcharts and applications;
- 2. producing clean and efficient specifications, integrating software components
- 3. verifying and deploying systems and programs
- 4. troubleshooting and upgrading existing software,
- 5. debugging errors
- 6. Executing improvements, assisting in creation of technical documentation for reports and references.

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

Pong agencies ecommerce shop

https://pongafrica.shop/

Final year project

Plant disease detection using CNN

GitHub: https://github.com/bethwelmusin/Diseaseprediction-project

UONBI & MOH MIGORI Hackathon

Project: Data visualization

Link https://mohvisualizationapp.herokuapp.com/admin/dashboard

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Traveling, playing computer games, and socializing

REFEREES

Jesse Muraya

CEO, Pong agencies Limited

Tel: 0720472020

Cornelius Tonui

CEO, Micropoint Systems Limited

Tel: 0720472020

Mr. Nixom Amuomo,

Rongo University Faculty Advisor,

Tel: +254 724484257